DENNIS-IMMANUEL CZOGALLA Resume

d.czogalla@outlook.com
https://github.com/denczo
(+61) 493 313 697

SUMMARY ___

Curious and highly motivated full stack developer with 5+ years experience in the industry. Proficient with React, Javascript and Typescript. Excels at problem-solving, creative thinking and teamwork skills which allows to deliver suitable solutions within a given deadline. Seeking to become a valuable member of the team and to contribute to the success of the company.

Experience

CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST 01/2021 - 05/2023

Vivents GmbH

Heidelberg, Germany

- collaborated with an interdisciplinary team to develope an online platform to host and manage virtual events with 300+ user
- improved the reliability and stability of the platform's chat by refactoring existing components and implemented new features to improve the user experience (ReactJS, Typescript, GraphQL, Sass)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER 09/2019 - 12/2020

German Cancer Research Center

Heidelberg, Germany

- collaborated with two Scrum-Teams to develope software which support doctors in the planning of cancer treatment and to collect medical data of volunteer participants for scientific research
- transformed medical data of 200k patients of existing databases for further analysis (JAVA, JDBC)
- setup of an database infrastructure for faster data queries which automatically receives the latest data of external scientific databases on a daily basis (SQL, SQL Dumps, Bash Script, Linux)

INTERN & WORKING STUDENT

02/2017 - 08/2019

Heidelberg, Germany

Edataconsulting GmbH

- collaborated with an international team to research and prototype VR & AR applications
- developed an AR application which has been used on fairs and exhibitions to promote and showcase the company interactively (Unity, C#, Microsoft Hololens)

INTERN 05/2013 - 07/2013

Acteno Energy GmbH

Heidelberg, Germany

• improved data visualisation of the company's internal software which monitors power consumption of their clients (C#. ASP.NET)

Education _____

UNIVERSITY OF MANNHEIM

02/2014 - 08/2019

B.Sc. in Computer Science

Mannheim, Germany

Thesis describes architecture for convolutional autoencoder to classify images on Raspberry Pi Zero

SRH TECHNICAL SCHOOL

10/2011 - 10/2013

Training in Computer Sciences for game- and multimedia development

Heidelberg, Germany

Skills_____

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE Experienced: Typescript/Javascript, Python, Java, C#, CSS/Sass, HTML, SQL

Familiar: Bash Scripting | GraphQL

LIBRARIES & FRAMEWORKS ReactJS, MobX, Tailwind CSS, Framer Motion, Numpy, Matplotlib, Kivy, Tkinter

TOOLS Git | Linux | REST | VSCode | Docker | Unity | Blender | Photoshop

LANGUAGES Native: German | Fluent: English